[
  {
    "question": "Which planet is covered largely by water?",
    "choice1": "Venus",
    "choice2": "Earth",
    "choice3": "Mars",
    "choice4": "Moon",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": " What is the name of the highest peak on Mars? ",
    "choice1": "Olympus",
    "choice2": "Bristol",
    "choice3": "Oxford",
    "choice4": "Cannon",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet is known for its spectacular icy rings",
    "choice1": "Mars",
    "choice2": "Earth",
    "choice3": "Saturn",
    "choice4": "Uranus",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet is the furthest from the sun?",
    "choice1": "Earth",
    "choice2": "Neptune",
    "choice3": "Saturn",
    "choice4": "Uranus",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the largest planet of our solar system?",
    "choice1": "Jupiter",
    "choice2": "Neptune",
    "choice3": "Mars",
    "choice4": "Venus",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet is the hottest planet of the solar system? ",
    "choice1": "Venus",
    "choice2": "Earth",
    "choice3": "Mars",
    "choice4": "Moon",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet is known for the \"Great Red Spot\"? ",
    "choice1": "Neptune",
    "choice2": "Venus",
    "choice3": "Mars",
    "choice4": "Jupiter",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet is the fastest planet?",
    "choice1": "Mars",
    "choice2": "Earth",
    "choice3": "Mercury",
    "choice4": "Sun",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet is the most likely candidate for a future human habitat?",
    "choice1": "Mars",
    "choice2": "Moon",
    "choice3": "Mercury",
    "choice4": "Sun",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet is named after the Roman goddess of beauty?",
    "choice1": "Mars",
    "choice2": "Earth",
    "choice3": "Mercury",
    "choice4": "Venus",
    "answer": "4"
  }
]
